<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<comments>
  <node>Since this happened we have seen a big difference in the class.</node>
  <node>We understand each other better.</node>
  <node>Boys dont hate each other now.</node>
  <node>I*#3*m more confident now, I play with everyone now.</node>
  <node>Everybody now gets along better</node>
  <node>We*#3*re more together as a class</node>
  <node>The stances teach you about yourself and help you describe yourself better.</node>
  <node>Before these classes I just thought I was happy or sad but now I know my stances and I can stance myself.</node>
  <node>I liked it because it gave you something to work towards.</node>
  <node>I thought I was a hard worker but I think now there are times I could be more actively engaged. So there*#3*s a way to improve.</node>
  <node>It made me think about how to deal with annoying people in my group and people who boss me about. I didn*#3*t really know what I could do before. I can stance other people now and I deal with them better.</node>
  <node>It was interesting to learn more about why people behave differently. I know how I behave, but I hadn*#3*t really thought about why.</node>
  <node>The stance diary stops you going into denial about your behaviour. It helps you face up to your behaviour.</node>
  <node>The stances really made me think about what kind of person I am.</node>
  <node>I used to think pupils were good and bad but now I know there is a whole range of stances, its*#3* given me a bigger picture.</node>
  <node>I know a lot of stroppy people and it*#3*s helped me deal with them.</node>
  <node>If you are upset and angry you concentrate on what is making you upset and angry, not your work.</node>
  <node>You can look back at your earlier stances and see how you*#3*ve changed.</node>
  <node>There are parts of yourself that the teacher knows but you don*#3*t and this helps you find out about it.</node>
  <node>This asks you questions I*#3*ve always wanted to be asked but never have.</node>
</comments>